I know you'll look the other way
I know you long for something new
So there you're wasting all your day
Looking for something that was right in front of you
And I just want them to notice you
And I, I'll never let go of you
There's something flying in the air
And I just don't know what it could be
Smoke is flying everywhere
I'm getting the feeling it's the end for you and me
And I, I know that we might be through
But I, I'll never let go of you
I'll never let go of you
I know you'll look the other way
I know you long for something new
So there you're wasting all your day
Looking for something that was right in front of you
And I just want them to notice you
And I, I'll never let go of you
There's something flying in the air
And I just don't know what it could be
Smoke is flying everywhere
I'm getting the feeling it's the end for you and me
And I, I know that we might be through
But I, I'll never let go of you
I'll never let go of you
By RentAnAdviser.com